World War 3.0
Zero Days is a documentary film directed by Alex Gibney.
Alex Gibney explores the phenomenon of Stuxnet, a self-replicating
computer virus discovered in 2010 by international IT experts.
Evidently commissioned by the US and Israeli governments, this malware was
designed to specifically sabotage Iran’s nuclear programme.
However, the complex computer worm ended up not only infecting its
intended target but also spreading uncontrollably.
Self, played by Yossi Melman.
Self, played by Ralph Langner.
Self, played by Emad Kiyaei.
Self, played by Richard A. Clarke.
Self, played by Eric Chien.
Self, played by Liam O'Murchu.
Zero Days is a 2016 American documentary film directed by Alex Gibney.
It was selected to compete for the Golden Bear at the
66th Berlin International Film Festival.
The tone is thought_provoking.